[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けっこんします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Виходити заміж, одружуватися"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とうろくします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Реєструвати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とうろく' read in word?",
        "answer": "реєстрація"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'つりします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Рибалити"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいぎします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Проводити засідання"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいぎ' read in word?",
        "answer": "засідання, конференція"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょくじします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Їсти"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょくじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "їжа"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいものします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Робити покупки"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいもの' read in word?",
        "answer": "покупки"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなかがすきました' read in word?",
        "answer": "Я зголоднів “Живіт став пустим”"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなかがいっぱい' read in word?",
        "answer": "Я ситий “Живіт став повним"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のどがかわきました' read in word?",
        "answer": "Хочу пити “Горло пересохло”"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そうしましょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Так і поступимо (вираження згоди)”"
    }
]
